everestcasino.com 2011-12-13

# On-line Casino Online casino privacy policy at Everest Casino

Overview

Legal Disclaimer

Agreement

Bonus Terms

Crystal Points Terms

Summit Points Terms

Transfer Policy

Refer-A-Friend

Disconnect Bet Protection

VIP Summit Club

Privacy Policy

Official Rules

|  |  |  | 

Version No: 1.0  
Date of Issue: August 5, 2011 

Everest Gaming (Gibraltar) Limited ("we", "us", "Everest") runs and operates the following websites and brands: [www.everestcasino.com](http://www.everestcasino.com/) and [www.everestpoker.com](http://www.everestpoker.com/) ("the Sites"). The group of companies of which Everest is a part includes Everest and any holding company or subsidiary of Everest or any subsidiary of any such holding company and any company associated with such holding company or subsidiary ("Group").

Everest is committed to treating your personal data as highly confidential and to observing all applicable laws on data protection during all stages of the processing of your personal data. Please take the time to read our Privacy Policy carefully.

**Personal Data:** All references to 'personal data' in this Privacy Policy refer to any personal information about a natural person which enables that individual to be identified directly or indirectly by reference to the data provided.

**Collection of Information:** We collect the following information about you when you register on the Sites: first name, surname, date of birth, postal address, email address, phone number (optional), language and secret question. You will also be required to provide login details of your choice, namely a username, screen name, password and an answer to the secret question which will be kept by us. We additionally require you to provide us with a payment method and payment details (for example in relation to your credit card, bank transfer or another acceptable means of payment) in order that you can credit your Everest account. We may also request that you send us a copy of an official document for identification purposes. We collect, retain and use information about you only for the purpose of providing superior gaming services to you and to comply with applicable legislation. Most of this information is supplied by you on a voluntary basis, and some is gathered automatically by our systems (such as your choice of games and payment preferences). We will protect your personal information and respect your privacy in accordance with best business practices and applicable laws.

**Amendments to Personal Data:** You have the right to make any alterations to any personal data which we hold which may have changed, become obsolete or which may be inaccurate. Should you believe that any personal data which we hold about you is incorrect, please contact Player Support referring to the data which you would like to modify and we will amend any personal data which is found to be incorrect.

**Use of Information:** The information is used to protect and administer any records, accounts or data related to you; to help complete a transaction initiated by you; to comply with certain laws and regulations; to help us design and enhance our services so that we may provide you with quality services and player support; and to communicate with you about updates to our software, services, and/or websites. We may send you emails from time to time containing information ranging from special promotions to technical and other information relating to our services and to the services of our Group companies. Should you wish to unsubscribe from our email mailing list, you can do this easily by either changing your Account settings or clicking "unsubscribe" on the bottom of the email. Please note that we may from time to time send out service-related emails and it is therefore recommended that you do not opt out of receiving emails from Everest.

**Third parties:** As part of our partnership with commercial banks and/or the companies in charge of verifying the authenticity of credit card or electronic payment processing data, your details are at the disposal of these establishments. However, these establishments are only entitled to use such information for legal investigation purposes. We may also enter into partnerships with data processors and companies which provide security, age verification, fraud detection and identification verification services in order to improve the efficiency and security of the Sites or to comply with relevant regulations. These companies may have access to your personal data in order that they can process necessary information data and maintain the security of the Sites. The companies that we choose to carry out these functions have strict policies regarding privacy of personal data, although we accept no responsibility for the privacy policies of those companies. We will not disclose the amount of your winnings or losses to any person or third party other than to you unless we are required by law to disclose such information to competent authorities. It is therefore incumbent upon you to declare your winnings to the relevant authorities if you reside in a country where such gains are subject to taxation. We reserve the right to pass on to public or other relevant authorities, customers' personal data if necessary or required in the course of any legal investigation.

**Keeping Information Private:** We do not license, sell, rent or trade any personal information, including contact data or specific information about your accounts or other personal data, to any third party or to any other players. In order to provide you with an efficient service, we and/or our service providers may require the transfer of your personal data from one country to another on a world-wide basis, and/or to other commonly-owned corporate entities. Everest is committed to taking all necessary steps to ensure that whenever personal data is transferred, such transfer takes place solely within the Group and/or the Group's select partners in which companies the standards of privacy and confidentiality should be of an acceptable standard, irrelevant of location. You hereby consent to your personal data being so transferred. Everest shall in no manner whatsoever be held responsible for the manner in which third parties process the personal data of our customers. Everest shall only be responsible for its own Privacy Policy and it does not warrant the standard of the privacy policies of any of the third parties who may have links placed on our Sites. We strongly recommend that when you access a new page via a link on our Site(s) which takes you to an external website, you take time to read through the privacy policy of the new website which you enter.

**Non-Personal Information:** For research or promotional purposes, we may use non-personal, non-specific information to generate statistics on general player activity, including transaction patterns, payout amounts and gaming preferences, but these initiatives will never include any personally identifiable information without authorized player consent.

**Retention of personal data:** As our customer, you or we can close your Everest account at any time. Following closure of your account, we will retain your personal data on record for as long as required by law.

**Protection of Minors:** The services which Everest offers are strictly prohibited for persons under 18 years of age or under the age of legal consent for using online gaming services under the laws of the jurisdiction in which the person is located. Consequently, minors may not register on our Sites and should not provide us with any personal data. We collect proof of identification from our customers as part of our age verification process. Any minor who is found to be gambling on Everest shall have any winnings confiscated and his/her account will be immediately blocked. Everest reserves the right to conduct a security review to validate your identity and age. Your acceptance of our Privacy Policy authorises us to conduct such security reviews which may include ordering of credit reports or verification of the information supplied by you against third party databases.

**Protection of Information:** We have implemented a number of security measures to safeguard your information. It is protected on secure networks and is accessible by a limited number of employees who have special access rights to such systems. When you access areas containing your personal player information, we use a secure server connection. Industry-standard encryption technologies are used when transferring or receiving sensitive information supplied by you. We update and test our technology on a regular basis to improve the protection of your information and to ensure the integrity of our systems. Although we endeavour to do our best to ensure the protection and privacy of your personal data at all times, we cannot guarantee that the performance of our service will be free from error at all times. Should any such error have an effect or consequence on the privacy of your personal data, we shall not be liable in any manner whatsoever in damages or otherwise.

**Cookies:** A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Cookies help us to provide you with a better Site. We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. For the session ID cookie, once users close the browser, the cookie simply terminates. A persistent cookie is a small text file stored on the user's hard drive for an extended period of time. Some of our business partners use cookies on our Sites (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies once we have given permission for our partners to set cookies for advertising. We use cookies with your permission to remember information about your Site preferences (for example, the language you use on the Site). You may decline to accept cookies but this will prevent you from taking full advantage of the Site and your user experience of the Site will be reduced.

**Log Files:** Like most standard website servers we use log files. This includes IP addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the Site, track user's movement in the aggregate and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use.

**Profile:** We store information that we collect through cookies and log files to create a profile of our users. A profile is stored information that we keep on individual users that detail their viewing preferences. Consequently, the information we collect is tied to the user's personally identifiable information to provide relevant offers and to improve the content of the Site for the user. Your profile is used to tailor your visit to our Site and to direct marketing promotions to you which we feel you would be interested in. We do not share your profile with other third parties outside of companies within our Group.

**Modifications:** It may become necessary, at any time, for us to make modifications to this Privacy Policy. The purpose of such modifications may be to further simplify user processes or to further reinforce security measures in order to upgrade to future technological innovations. Continued use of the Sites by any registered Player after any modifications to this Privacy Policy will be considered as acceptance thereof. It is the responsibility of each Player to regularly check the Privacy Policy for updates.  
  
---|---|---|---|---
